Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records WAG.124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX: CWA Administration, 1947-1989
  - Subseries IX:B: Central File, 1947-1989
    - Notice to Mediation Agencies, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Calhoun County Board of Supervisors, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: District 7, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 20)
    - Deletion of Company, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 21)
    - Mountain Bell Health Care Survey, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 22)
    - Mountain Bell, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Executive Vice President, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 24)
    - Agreement: Electro-Media, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 25)
    - Agreement: Magic Valley Cable Vision, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 26)
    - Agreement: Executone-Central Idaho, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 27)
    - Agreement: Monkal, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Executive Vice President, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 29)
    - Agreement: Health and Environment Dept., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 30)
    - Agreement: Tel. Innovations Corp., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 31)
    - Agreement: Pacif. Bell Business Plan, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 32)
    - CPI, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 33)
    - Agreement: Letters of Understanding, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 34)
    - Nevada Bell, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 35)
    - Agreement: Robinson Bros. Construction, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 36)
    - Memorandum of Agreement, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 37)
    - Agreement: WUI-TAS, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 38)
    - Agreement: Standard Utility Contractors, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 39)
    - Agreement: Unisec, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 40)
    - Agreement: Wash. County, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 41)
    - Agreement: Cable Oakland, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 42)
    - Agreement: Northern Tel. Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 43)
    - Agreement: American Business Com, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 44)
    - Contract 300 Lenora, Seattle, WA, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 45)
    - Deletion of Company: Subway Construction, Seattle WA, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 46)
    - Nevada Bell Self Provisioning Plans, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 47)
    - Contract: Williamette Subscription Television, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 48)
    - Articles of Agreement: Associated Elec. Co., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 49)
    - Agreement: Aztec Communications, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 50)
    - Company Number Assignment: Aztec. Communications, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 51)
    - Henkels & McCoy, Inc. and Delinquent Dues, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 52)
    - Contract: Cascade Tele., Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 53)
    - Liberty Cable Television, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 54)
    - Articles of Agreement: Riedel - Standard, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 55)
    - Company Number Assignment: COMGROUP National, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 56)
    - Agreement: Tel. Utilities of Wash., Cascade Auto. Co. & L. 9103, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 57)
    - Collective Bargaining: Company Number Assn. & Agreement: Protective Tech, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 58)
    - Company Number Assignment; Collective Bargaining Agreement & Office Comm. Service, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 59)
    - Company Number Assignment; Agreement: Overall Pacific Communications, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 60)
    - Company Number Assignment; Agreement: Horizon Sev Systems, Collective Bargaining, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 61)
    - Company Number Assignment and Contract: Teknon Corp, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 62)
    - Company Number Assignment and Contract: United Communications Systems, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 63)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement: S& F Cabling, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 64)
    - Company Number Assignment: S&F Cabling, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 65)
    - Tele. Comm. Workers Agreement, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 66)
    - CWA Labor Management Pension Fund, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 67)
    - GTE Negot. Health Insurance, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 68)
    - Memorandum of Agreement, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 69)
    - GTE Negotiations, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 70)
    - Agreement between Group W Cable, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 71)
    - Agreement: Star Construction Co., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 72)
    - Agreement: Wright and Lopez, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 291, Folder 73)
    - Memorandum of Employee Representation Policy, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 74)
    - Agreement between Sammons Communications, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 75)
    - United Inter-Mountain Telephone Co. Pension Proposals, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 76)
    - CWA Memorandum with Collective Bargaining Pension Plans, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 77)
    - Agreement: A.D.T. Co., 1984-1986 (Box 291, Folder 78)
    - Agreement: Continental Tel. Of South Alabama, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 79)
    - Agreement: Group W Cable, Inc., 1984 (Box 291, Folder 80)
    - GTE Negotiations, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 81)
    - ALLTEL Telephone System Contract, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 82)
    - Kentron International, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 83)
    - Memorandum of Agreement, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 84)
    - Agreement: Ame. Dist. Tel. Co., 1984-1985 (Box 291, Folder 85)
    - Correspondence: Apache Moving and Storage, 1984 (Box 291, Folder 86)
    - Agreement: New Orleans Bell Tel. Employees Federal Credit Union No. 44, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Agreement: North Central Tel. Cooperative, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement: Twin Lakes Tel. Corp., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Agreement: J.L.C. Corp., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Agreement: Telescripps Cable Co. of Knoxville, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement: Knoxville Telescripps Cable, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Agreement: Hayes Int'l. Corp., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Agreement: Times Mirror Cable T.V. of Eastern Kentucky, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Miss. Telco Fed. Credit Union, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - Collective Bargaining Agreement: Birmingham Cable Communications, 1984-1985 (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Company Number Assignment, Management Svcs., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Company Number Assignment, TWB Communications Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 12)
    - Agreement between CWA and Management Svcs., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 13)
    - Company Number Assignment, Clairborne Elec. Coop. Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: General, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Local 11555 (Understanding of Engagement) and Update, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Grievances, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Locals (Complin Letters, Local 11590 Contract), 1984 (Box 292, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Deletion Notice, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: A.D.T. Contract Analysis, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Complaint Letter, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Delinquent Dues, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Units Deleted, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Units Deleted, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Units Deleted, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Delinquent Dues, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Executive Board, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Union Dues deductions, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Delinquent Dues, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Units Deleted, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Deletion of Com., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Units Deleted, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Omni Cable Services, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Unit Deleted, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence: Company Numbers Assignment, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence: GTE & AT & T Agreement, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence: Texas AFL-CIO (Operator Services; A New Strategy for a Better Work Place), 1984 (Box 292, Folder 46)
    - Letter of Agreement: Dallas Works, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 47)
    - Change in Company Information, Agreement: Group W Cable, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 48)
    - Contract: Communications Corp. of America, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 49)
    - Labor Agreement: Helena Labs., 1983 (Box 292, Folder 50)
    - Deletion of Company: G.P.I. Corp., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 51)
    - Deletion of Company: RMI Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 52)
    - Deletion of Company: Tele. Resources Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 53)
    - Agreement between Austin Regional Clinic, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 54)
    - Company Number Assignment: Express Comms., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 55)
    - Company Number Assignment: Southwestern Bell Media, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 56)
    - Company Number Assignment: Southwestern Bell Yellow Pages Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 57)
    - Company Number Assignment: Ad/Vent Grafix Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 58)
    - Company Number Assignment: SW Bell Pubns. Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 59)
    - Company Number Assignment: Ad/Vent Info. Svcs. Inc., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 60)
    - District 13 Ass't., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Communications, Jan 1984-Mar 1984 (Box 292, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Communications, Apr 1984-May 1984 (Box 292, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Communications, Jun 1984-Jul 1984 (Box 292, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Communications, Aug 1984 (Box 292, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Communications, Sep 1984-Oct 1984 (Box 292, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Communications, Nov 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 292, Folder 67)
    - Correspondence: CWA Meeting /General Materials, Jan 1984-Sep 1984 (Box 292, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Tech. Force Surplus., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Technologies, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 70)
    - Correspondence: Independent Tel. Bargaining Schedule, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence: AT&T Com., 1984 (Box 292, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence: Locals, 1984 (Box 292, Folder 73)
    - United System Contracts and Benefits Analysis, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Bargaining Proposals, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Continental Tel. System Contracts Analysis, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Contract Tel. System Contracts Analysis, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Defense Fund/Central System Local Presidents' Conference, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - ALLTel System Contracts Analysis, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - ADT Financial Analysis, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - National T.V. Cable company profile, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - ATTIS, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - CWA/ATTIS, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - CWA/ATTIS, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - CWA/ATTIS; Sales of Equipment to Retails), 1984 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - CWA/ATTIS; Sales of Equipment to Retails), 1984 (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - CWA/ATTIS, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 14)
    - CWA/ATTIS, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 15)
    - CWA/ATTIS (Surplus, Technologies), 1984 (Box 293, Folder 16)
    - CWA/ATTIS (Surplus, Region 5), 1984 (Box 293, Folder 17)
    - Federation of Telephone Workers of PA, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 18)
    - FTWP/CWA, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: President, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 20)
    - AT&T Bargaining, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 21)
    - AT&T Arbitration Case, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 22)
    - Arbitration Awards, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 23)
    - Bargaining Council Meeting, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, Aug 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1986-1987 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 1, 1987 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 1, 1987-1988 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 1, 1988 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1985 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 2, 1986-1988 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 3, 1986-1988 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1986-1987 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 4, 1987 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 4, 1986-1988 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 6, 1986-1988 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 7, 1986-1988 (Box 294, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1987 (Box 294, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 9, 1987-1988 (Box 294, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 9, 1987-1988 (Box 294, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, District 13, 1987-1988 (Box 294, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1986-1987 (Box 294, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1987 (Box 294, Folder 19)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1985-1986 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1982-1983 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1984 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1980-1982 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1977-1979 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1977-1979 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1974-1978 (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1975-1977 (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1966-1973 (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1970-1974 (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 1, 1980-1986 (Box 295, Folder 11)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 2, 1974-1979 (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 2, 1968-1977 (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 3, 1980-1986 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 3, 1964-1971 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 3, 1970-1979 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 4, 1979-1985 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 4, 1982-1986 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 4, 1977-1979 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 4, 1977-1979 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 4, 1965-1976 (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 4, 1971-1976 (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 5, 1984-1986 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 5, 1981-1984 (Box 296, Folder 11)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 5, 1977-1979 (Box 296, Folder 12)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 5, 1963-1976 (Box 296, Folder 13)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 6, 1984-1986 (Box 296, Folder 14)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 6, 1980-1983 (Box 296, Folder 15)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 6, 1974-1979 (Box 296, Folder 16)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 6, 1966-1973 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 6, 1966-1973 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 7, 1980-1982 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 7, 1982-1986 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 7, 1975-1979 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 7, 1966-1974 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 8, 1980-1986 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 8, 1975-1979 (Box 297, Folder 8)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 8, 1966-1974 (Box 297, Folder 9)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 9, 1983-1986 (Box 297, Folder 10)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 9, 1983-1986 (Box 297, Folder 11)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 9, 1980-1983 (Box 297, Folder 12)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 9, 1978-1979 (Box 297, Folder 13)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 9, 1976-1977 (Box 297, Folder 14)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 9, 1974-1976 (Box 297, Folder 15)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 9, 1966-1973 (Box 297, Folder 16)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 10, 1979-1982 (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 10, 1983-1986 (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 10, 1974-1976 (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 10, 1977-1979 (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 10, 1964-1974 (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 11, 1984 (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 11, 1985-1986 (Box 298, Folder 7)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 11, 1981-1983 (Box 298, Folder 8)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 11, 1980-1983 (Box 298, Folder 9)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 11, 1977-1979 (Box 298, Folder 10)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 11, 1973-1977 (Box 298, Folder 11)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 12, 1981-1986 (Box 298, Folder 12)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 12, 1974-1979 (Box 298, Folder 13)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, Canada, 1967-1973 (Box 298, Folder 14)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, District 13, 1984-1986 (Box 298, Folder 15)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, Various Districts, 1988 (Box 298, Folder 16)
    - CWA Staff Roster, 1986 (Box 298, Folder 17)
    - Organizing: Company Recruitment, Various Districts, 1968-1985 (Box 298, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1974-1982 (Box 298, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1963-1976 (Box 298, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, 1981-1986 (Box 298, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Training, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - John Kulstad's Memo of 1/16 regarding Local Leadership Schools, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - John B. Kulstad, Local Training Conference: Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Task Force for Economic Growth, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Public Education: Reports and Flyers, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Public Education: Reports and Information: Flyers, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Meeting on Technology and Labor Relations, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - Taking Action For Excellence; Task Force, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Making It Happen; A Positive Guide to the Future, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Executive Vice President, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 11)
    - Minimum Standards for CSI Contracts (attached), 1984 (Box 299, Folder 12)
    - CWA National Training Fund, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 13)
    - IBEW Analysis (8/1), 1984 (Box 299, Folder 14)
    - Communications Systems Industry, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 15)
    - Report from CSI Conference, 1984 (Box 299, Folder 16)
    - Attached NTEC Background Material, 1984 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Call and Buy Union Info, 1984 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Conferences, Training, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Training Program/Training School, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - District 8 Leadership Conference, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Leadership School, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Conferences/Education Task Force/University Programs, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - National Employee Ownership, Participation Conference at Guilford College, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - College Seminars, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Conferences, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Northern Telecom Reps. Meeting, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 11)
    - Union-Busting, Northern Telecom, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 12)
    - CSI Contracts, ISDN, Call and Buy Union Campaign, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 13)
    - Legislation, Jan 1984 (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Legislation, Feb 1984 (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, Mar 1984 (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Legislation, Apr 1984-May 1984 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Legislation, Jun 1984-Jul 1984 (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Legislation, Aug 1984 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Legislation, Sep 1984-Oct 1984 (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, Nov 1984 (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Legislation, Dec 1984 (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - Legislative, Jan 1985 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Legislative, Feb 1985 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Legislative, Mar 1985 (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - Legislative, Apr 1985 (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - Legislative, May 1985-Jun 1985 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - Legislative, Jul 1985 (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - Legislative, Aug 1985 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - Legislative, Sep 1985 (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - Legislative, Oct 1985 (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - Legislative, Nov 1985 (Box 302, Folder 10)
    - Legislative, Dec 1985 (Box 302, Folder 11)
    - Healthcare/ Technological Change, Jan 1984-Feb 1984 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Economics/Quality of Worklife, Mar 1984 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - ESOP's, Michigan Conference, Training Program, Apr 1984 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Issues, May 1984-Jun 1984 (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - Legislative, Jan 1985 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Legislative, Feb 1985 (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - Legislative, Mar 1985 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - Legislative, Apr 1985 (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - QWL, Personnel Letters, May 1985 (Box 303, Folder 9)
    - Rpt. On Regional Bell Operating Co., Jun 1985 (Box 303, Folder 10)
    - Training Programs, Wages, Economic Issues, Jul 1985 (Box 303, Folder 11)
    - Economics, Technology Changes, Aug 1985 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Wages, Slide Presentation, Sep 1985 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - Training, Bargaining Proposal, Oct 1985 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Pension Plan, HMO's, Nov 1985 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Pension Plan, Training, Dec 1985 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Computers, Feb 1985 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Sperry Computers, Mar 1985 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Computers, Apr 1985-May 1985 (Box 304, Folder 8)
    - Special Election Mailing, Jun 1985-Jul 1985 (Box 304, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, Mar 1979-Aug 1985, 1985 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, Mar 1985-Oct 1985 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Equipment Acquisition, Nov 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Secretary Treasurer, Aug 1985 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Executive Vice President, 1985 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Non-print materials, 1985 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Life Membership Cards, 1985 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: CWA Publications, 1985 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Speeches, 1985 (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: President, 1985 (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, Jan 1985 (Box 305, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, Apr 1985 (Box 305, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, May 1985 (Box 305, Folder 13)
    - Clippings, Jun 1985 (Box 305, Folder 14)
    - Clippings, Jul 1985 (Box 305, Folder 15)